(Leonard:)It only gets funnier
when you explain it, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)I know.
(Howard:)Okay, she's all settled in the guest room.
(Bernadette:)Maybe we should get one of those
machines to help her up the stairs.
(Howard:)You mean a forklift?
(Bernadette:)-Howie...
-I'm sorry.
(Howard:)I just can't deal
with this right now.
(Bernadette:)Taking care of your own mother?
How can you say that?
(Howard:)Bernie, she's gonna be off her feet
for six to eight weeks.
(Howard:)Are you prepared to feed her,
wash her and take her to the toilet?
(Bernadette:)-I would do it for my mother.
-Yeah, of course you would.
(Howard:)You're a loving person.
(Howard:)I'm what my people would call a putz.
(Bernadette:)Look, I'm not crazy about the idea,
but what other choice do we have?
(Howard:)We get a nurse. Preferably someone
from a third world country
(Howard:)who's used to suffering
and unpleasant smells.
(Bernadette:)You'd hire a total stranger
to take care
(Bernadette:)of the woman who raised you?
That's so cruel.
(Howard:)Not if we pay them well